

Elekwachi Christian Chidiebube

Number 10 nworie lane amakohia 09134083460 | elekwachichristian464@gmail.com in linkedin.com/in/christian-elekwachi

Objective

I am a software developer with more than two years of experience. My goal is to enhance my professional skills, capabilities and knowledge in an organization which recognizes the value of hard work and trusts me with responsibilities and challenges.

Experience

• Sotechapps 2019 - 2021

Graphics designer

- Created creative advertising content for various media including business cards, flyers, posters, banners generating 40% increase in company revenue.
- Created e-commerce app and website contents for company use.
- Collaborated with other designers and performance team on designing updates to apps thereby improving user experience by 60%.

Leopeige Cleaning

2021 - Present

Web developer

- Design and establish user friendly website that guarantees high traffic, page views and maximum user experience generating a 55% increase in the company's revenue.
- Fixed bugs from existing website improving functionality by 25%
- Made research and suggestions for website improvement.

Max concepts

2020 - Present

Graphics designer

- Designed visual contents for social media posts which received over 1000 points of engagement.
- o Created designs that effectively communicated the brands message to target audience.
- Created graphics designs for a wide range of clients ranging from small businesses to large companies.

• Sotechapps 2021 - Present

Web developer

- Managed web design projects from start to finish using HTML, CSS and Javascript with 100% client satisfaction.
- Built responsive, accessible and dynamic webpages to enable users to easily navigate website.

Pearlz and gem beauty

2021 - 2022

Graphics designer

- Effectively communicated with clients to ensure successful outcomes.
- Designed attractive flyers and graphics for social media posts increasing engagements by 55%
- Co-operated effectively with designing team to develop outstanding graphics.

Sotechapps

2019 - Present

Product video ads creator

- Working knowledge of adobe premier pro, after effects, kinemaster, inshot.
- Created videos for advertising and social media distribution increasing engagements by

29%

• Ensured edited videoes were mistake free and media corrections when needed.

Education

 Federal University of Technology Owerri Software Engineering

Skills

- HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React.js | Bootstrap.
- MongoDB | Express is | Node.is | Php
- Adobe premiere pro | Adobe after effects | Kinemaster | Inshot.
- Color theory | Design | Typography and layout | Canva | Photoshop | Snapseed.

Projects

Leopeige Cleaning (GitHub)

https://christianeleks.github.io/neat/Leopeige Cleaning/

Previous design works

https://bit.ly/G-designs

Product video ads

https://bit.ly/g-works

Reference

• Dike Adrian Obinna - Sotechapps

Manager Sotechapps dikeobinna66@yahoo.com

Gift Chukwuemeka - Max concepts

C.E.O Max concepts giftchukwuemeka012@gmail.com

Abanukam Jennifer U. - Starry_Consults

Manager ajenniferfelix@gmail.com